I will become a Cinder Nova who shines even brighter than Anchan did! I swear I will!
And even if I become the Cinder Nova, I will not disappear!
Since her shocking declaration of her desire to become the Cinder Nova,
9th generation Yugo Oshima's popularity has been rising rapidly!
Yugo's just so inspiring!
Such intensity!
I'm in love!
The election of 75th generation trainee Memori Kishida
and 77th generation trainee Chieri Soto has also sparked much discussion.
The next major event everyone is looking forward to is succession.
Currently, the trainee most likely to become a successor is...
I think it's Chieri-chan!
Memori's great, but Chieri's way more popular!
The right name for Chieri-chan? Hmm, that's a good question.
What about Mayu Yu?
You idiot, there's already Mark II. It'll be Jirina.
What? Not Ami?
With the elected member's first theater hall performance coming up, everyone...
Things are starting to get exciting!
A-chan...
Huh?
Hmm...
Oh my! The Kiraras of succession are buzzing with excitement!
Oh!
Am I crazy? Or was that the original A-chan?
Hurry! We have to inform Tsubasa-sama!
Shall I?
Do you?
Sm prosk
長い桜の前 未来があるなら 背を向けられない
ともよ覚えているかい あの日 誓い合ったこの場所
季節の花が咲く
主なきその声聞こえるよ 太陽がほら少しずつ当たりのその闇を剥がしてくれるだろ
主なきさあこの時に僕たちはそう歩き出そう 誰もみんな弱い生き物さ
愛の気配探しながら先へ進む
They even have gotten even more popular since they were elected
People are saying Chiyari might even succeed Achan. Crazy, huh?
Yeah, no kidding. At this rate, it may actually be possible.
We've got to make sure we don't fall behind.
Hey! Let's chat more work.
Okay, Chiyari will succeed Achan.
Ah-Chan.
Really now? So you're going to succeed Ah-Chan?
Please don't joke about that.
Is there someone else you want to succeed?
That's not what I meant.
I would be happy to succeed anyone.
It'd be a great honor no matter who it was.
That goes for all of us.
But everyone would love to be Ah-Chan.
One, two, three, four.
I don't care which it is. Just show me something today.
Eyes forward. Everyone ready?
The show's tomorrow. Let's bust our butts!
Right!
Hey, that photographer. What is she doing here?
You're in trouble, Buddha. You don't have your fake boobies, do ya?
No? Crap!
Make her feel welcome. Starting today, she will be our exclusive photographer.
It's a pleasure to be here.
I'm freelance photographer Mikako Minamino.
I'm actually your senior, fifth generation Minagishi Minami.
Or...
Just Mi-Chan.
What?!
Wow. It's really her.
You've got to be kidding!
Of course it is.
The fifth generation Mi-Chan is in one of the photos of the Centanovas back at the dormitory.
You should check them when we get back.
Good, good!
What's going on?
Entertainment regulations are getting more strict. It's made it hard for her to work.
What you're saying is she begged you for a job?
If it's truly your intention to bring back the Centanova position, I'll do everything I can to stop you. You can count on that.
Chan-chi! Nice smile! Chan-mi! Nice pose!
That's what incredible bodge you've got there! Show it off!
No one can stop them from shining as bright as they can, Mi-Chan.
Huh? Oh, are you worried about what I said on Atomistar?
Don't worry about it. I was just jealous. It's all good now.
Funny. I can't count the number of times I was jealous of you back when we were performing.
That's nice to hear, but I failed to become the Centanova back then.
You came closer than I did. Look after these girls for me.
You're shining, Mi-Chan.
I'm shining.
Alright.
That key balance!
But there's still just the more?
I...
I won't lose.
No matter what!
Am I crazy? Or has Nagisa been acting weird?
What? You think so?
Like Yuko-san!
Wow, they're terrible.
I don't see dynamic!
What is wrong with you?
Nagisa!
You too, Chieri!
Yuko-san?
What's up? Please tell me you're slacking.
You can shine so much brighter than that!
Sorry.
I guess she's done with practice for today.
Don't worry about Yuko. More importantly…
Nagisa!
Huh?
Come with me. We need to talk.
Okay. Is Yuko feeling alright?
Maybe she's feeling the pressure from winning first place.
And I'm Santa Claus.
Mayuyu, is something wrong?
Tsubasa, she left already.
She's just got a lot on her plate.
I feel a storm brewing! It's gonna go boom!
A storm brewing? You heard right!
There's a rumor that a new successor is about to be chosen!
The Keiraros of Succession showed the original Achan's image.
Does this mean someone will succeed her?
That's the only explanation.
Whoever succeeds her.
When the 14th generation Atsuko Medea is born…
Achan…
What will happen to you?
That light…
That was Achan's…
No doubt.
Nagisa Morimiya…
Or Chieri Sono…
Michan…
You think one of them might become Achan and it's eating you up?
Right on the money.
Michan…
Why did you stop shining?
Huh?
It's not that I stopped, I just couldn't.
You couldn't?
Why not?
It's hard to explain really.
Someone who's never been there wouldn't understand anyway.
Chanyu, you're into photography, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Those worthy of being the center nova have a certain sense.
It's not something that can be taught or acquired.
What sense?
They can seize a moment.
Their own brilliance resonates with others who shine in the same way.
They can capture the moment of that light.
Just like taking a picture.
You look at your subject and snap a shot at just the right moment.
And when you do that, then you can capture the light.
If that's really true, it might tell us which one will become Achan.
Of course.
It only works if you have the aptitude.
Yuko, what's wrong?
Oh, you're taking pictures! Take one of us!
Okay, sure.
Jerry and Nagisa?
I haven't seen them.
Thanks anyway!
Sonata, if you've got nothing better to do, train with me!
I'll pass.
Good call, Sonata. I wouldn't work that hard.
Your stomach will end up looking like a chocolate bar if you do.
Are you okay, Memori?
What are you talking about?
I don't know. You just seemed really beat.
I'm perfectly fine.
Cool.
Just checking.
Hey! Hey!
Huh?
Nagisa's late.
She said she'd be right here.
Oh, she's here!
Sorry, girls! It's just me!
Yuko-san?
Is something wrong?
You're on candid camera!
What?!
I understand you look up to Yuko a great deal.
However, trying to be like someone else won't make you a successor.
I understand. It's the nature of my soul, right?
That's not all.
Huh?
It's your ambition.
Ambition?
It's when your heart is looking at where it wants to be, then fights tooth and nail to get there.
Succession is about inheriting the ambition of a previous soul.
Inheriting the ambition of a previous soul.
Hmm.
Nagisa! Are you there?
Oh!
Yuko-san?
Chenmi looks like a model!
Her boobs are enormous!
Hey! Don't imitate Michan-san!
Hm? What was that?
Makoru's stomach growling!
Oh, right.
I guess it's about that time, isn't it?
Memori!
It's time for dinner.
Shall we go to the cafeteria, then?
Huh?
Memori!
Are you okay, Memori?
The Kiraras of Succession are doing it again!
Yuko-san!
Can I take a picture of you?
What?
Yeah, sure.
I guess that's okay.
Thanks a bunch!
Does this work?
Works for me!
But, uh…
Won't it be backlit?
It's fine!
Don't worry about that!
Trust me!
This is perfect!
Okay.
Huh.
I guess just taking a picture won't work.
Do you need another one or something?
Oh, no!
Don't worry about it!
Later!
Wait!
This afternoon at practice, what did you mean?
You said that Chiari and I could shine brighter than what we were.
I meant exactly what I said.
I said it because you two are my biggest rivals.
When it comes to the Center Nova.
The Center Nova?
You really mean that?
But I'm still only a trainee.
Uh…
In next year's general elections, I will!
I will definitely beat Ahchan and become the Center Nova!
Just you watch!
That's right.
So then, work on shining brighter.
Otherwise, it's not a competition, is it?
Hey, come quick!
Memori's sick!
Huh?
Memori-san?
The Kiraros of Succession displayed Memori's image.
Then…
Yes.
There's no mistaking this fever.
Memori's going to become a successor.
Well, I'll be.
Come to think of it, you had a fever just before your succession, right?
Yes.
It was just before a concert.
I got a fever and was groaning in my sleep.
A lot like Memori is now.
That was the first time I sensed it.
I felt Mariko Shinado's soul as if it were my own.
Huh.
Anyway, about tomorrow's concert, we need to choose an understudy, pronto.
Uh…
In that case…
If Memori can't perform, Nagisa, you will be her understudy.
This is completely up to you, though.
You'll have to learn the choreography in one night and perform in both concerts.
I can do it? Please, let me do it.
I'll practice with you.
I've been watching Memori dance.
I can help you get her part down.
Okay. Thanks, Chiyori.
Let's get started then.
Okay.
My ambition.
Not what Yuko-san wants.
Not what Chiyori wants.
But something I should aim for.
I don't know what that is yet, but…
Nagisa's acting different from how she was this afternoon.
Okay, maybe she's gotten a little bit better.
Hang in there, Memori.
Memori.
A succession fever.
Another successor will be born.
Lord.
It seems a new successor will be born soon.
It is very likely she will be the 14th generation, Medea Atsuko.
If that is true, she may become the center nova.
So, how is Chiyori?
As I understand it, she may be one of the candidates.
Chiyori.
You will become a shining star on stage.
And then I will be the sun shining on the galaxy.
Guess you weren't able to get a picture of the center nova shine.
Unless you're hiding it from me.
No way.
I don't need a lens.
I'll see it for myself.
In the place we shine the brightest.
Right here on stage.
Run stage!
走り出すバス追いかけて
僕は君に伝えたかった
こころのモヤモヤが消えて
I'm sorry. I told her to rest, but she insisted.
I have to perform.
For the wonderful fans who elected me.
For all of my friends and fellow members.
And the staff who so faithfully supported me.
Eizi, you can't perform in your condition.
Thanks for your concern. It's my responsibility as an elected member.
You're the one who loves me. I'm the one who loves you.
You're the one who loves me. I'm the one who loves me.
I'm the one who loves you.
Good, good!
She's amazing, isn't she?
That's the glow of an elected member.
Minori, I'm so proud of you.
Big sis?
I'll catch up to you.
Only those who overcome this test and receive Sensei-Sensei's approval
have any chance of becoming successors.
Minori,
I wonder who you will succeed.
Minori!
Her body's hot.
She's burning up!
Good job, Minori.
Leave the rest of to us, okay?
Nagisa, let's go.
Right.
No, I can still...
You need rest, Minori!
Nagisa! I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Please, let me do this! Let me sing and dance for you!
Where's Mimori?
Chan-na, he's taking over for Chan-myo, huh?
Chiri's keeping up with her!
This has got to be her!
Take your shirt!
There it is! That's what I've been waiting for!
Yuko-san, I will shine brighter than ever!
And when I do, I'll be the center nova!
That's the spirit rival, but you'll have to shine a lot brighter than that
if you hope to shine like Acha did!
I won't fall behind!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna shine brighter than ever!
Huh? Nagisa?
Is she crazy?!
What happened?!
Nagisa, we're still performing!
That's right! I, Nagisa Muromiya, will shine just as bright as Yuko-san and Chiri someday!
I want to become the center nova!
Bring it on, then!
Nagisa...
Nagisa!
She's so bright!
It can't be...
Thank you
Remember that flower is still in yei half
That Valentine's dream never completion
The flowers don't become any梨
The S dakar
The Sabor
May it start to shine
The yellow sound from the rays
Oh
The next concert will be a special concert
Memories Revolution
All right, let's celebrate
Who will she become
But to think you would succeed her name